I have been very away from you
yet it never felt that distant
Yes we had drifted apart
But it wasn’t mere distance that kept us apart
Your memories stayed with me, always
Your memories
With me
Days went by and the nights flew away
But you never came back
Even though your love was a lie
I just couldnt forget it
My love
I was never that far away from you
Your memories
Hooo ooo
Yes my life..
I have had so many countless nights
But you would have never known
I am teary-eyed right now
But you have never noticed
You have everything
From the earth to the sky
And the whole universe
And all I have is
Your memory
Hoooo oooo
Oh yes my life
There is only one wish in my heart
One and only prayer
Whether I exist or not
Just once in your life, once in your life
You think of me
The thought of me stays with you forever
Yes, my memory
“Hoooo oo ooo”
My memory..
With you…